http://www.cysticfibrosis.ca/privacy-policy

x
Ways to Give
Monthly
One-time (general)
In Honour
In Memory
Did you know that your version of Internet Explorer is out of date?
To get the best possible experience using our website we recommend downloading one of the browsers below.
Internet Explorer 10, Firefox, Chrome, or Safari.
All COVID-19 updates and resources can be found on the CF Canada website.
Privacy Policy
Cystic Fibrosis Canada (“CF Canada”) is committed to protecting the privacy and the confidentiality of personal information collected by CF Canada, from CF Canada employees, members, donors, volunteers, and other stakeholders. In order to comply with privacy legislation, we have developed a Privacy Policy. Any personally identifiable information which is not publicly available about our employees, members, donors, volunteers and other stakeholders is considered personal information, and will be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
Our Privacy Policy respects the ten foundational principles that form the basis of Canada’s Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (PIPEDA).
Details of our Privacy Policy are available by sending an e-mail to privacy@cysticfibrosis.ca with “Attention Privacy Officer” in the subject line, or by contacting CF Canada at 1-800-378-2233.
Updated – June 11, 2020
Upcoming Events
December 17, 2020
Alberta Annual 50/50 Raffle
Holiday Cheer 50/50 - Maximum prize $10,000!
Tickets on sale until December 17th 2020DRAW DATE:December 22nd, 2020
Purchase Tickets HERE. Read More
CF Champions
Patrick Kellar
Age 27, Peterborough, Ontario
Patrick is an inspiring, motivated individual that doesn’t let cystic fibrosis (CF) stand in his way of being successful. Diagnosed with CF at birth, Patrick has only looked at the positive side of things, often telling others that “It could be worse!” Read More
